let questions = [
	{
		id: 1,
		question: "\"Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony. Then, everything changed when ________ attacked.\"",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"the Water Tribes",
			"the Fire Nation",
			"the Earth Kingdom",
			"the Air Nomads"
		],
		correctAnswer: "the Fire Nation"
	},
	{
		id: 2,
		question: "Aang becomes an airbending master at the young age of _____",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"12",
			"6",
			"10",
			"16"
		],
		correctAnswer: "12"
	},
	{
		id: 3,
		question: "How long is Aang frozen in ice?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"50 years",
			"20 years",
			"100 years",
			"250 years"
		],
		correctAnswer: "100 years"
	},
	{
		id: 4,
		question: "What is the name of the Fire Nation prince tasked with finding the Avatar?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Jet",
			"Haru",
			"Zuko",
			"Bumi"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Zuko"
	},
	{
		id: 5,
		question: "Aang's flying bison is named...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Momo",
			"Fang",
			"Appa",
			"Naga"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Appa"
	},
	{
		id: 6,
		question: "What is Sokka's signature weapon that he inherited from his father?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"A sword",
			"A machete",
			"A katana",
			"A boomerang"
		],
		correctAnswer: "A boomerang"
	},
	{
		id: 7,
		question: "What is the name of the reigning Fire Lord?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Roku",
			"Ozai",
			"Sozin",
			"Azulon"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Ozai"
	},
	{
		id: 8,
		question: "The female warriors who fight using metal fans are the...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Freedom fighters",
			"Dai Li",
			"Kyoshi warriors",
			"White Lotus"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Kyoshi warriors"
	},
	{
		id: 9,
		question: "Aang and Katara learn waterbending from Master _____?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Pakku",
			"Yakone",
			"Arnook",
			"Unalaq"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Pakku"
	},
	{
		id: 10,
		question: "Which spirit is the guardian of the library of knowledge?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Wan",
			"Wan Shi Tong",
			"Koh",
			"Hei Bai"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Wan Shi Tong"
	},
	{
		id: 11,
		question: "Which location is believed to be the birthplace of earthbending?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Canal of Two Lovers",
			"Cave of Star Crossed Lovers",
			"Cave of Two Lovers",
			"Tunnel of Two Lovers"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Cave of Two Lovers"
	},
	{
		id: 12,
		question: "Team Avatar adopts a flying lemur and names it...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Fang",
			"Momo",
			"Flopsie",
			"Appa"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Momo"
	},
	{
		id: 13,
		question: "Which Avatar came right before Aang?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Kiyoshi",
			"Kuruk",
			"Roku",
			"Korra"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Roku"
	},
	{
		id: 14,
		question: "Bumi is the King of _______?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Ba Sing Se",
			"Omashu",
			"Hou-Ting",
			"Garsai"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Omashu"
	},
	{
		id: 15,
		question: "Admiral _____ was the leader of the Fire Nation Navy",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Zhao",
			"Kunyo",
			"Lu Ten",
			"Shyu"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Zhao"
	},
	{
		id: 16,
		question: "Princess ____ becomes the new moon spirit",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Korra",
			"Hama",
			"Yuri",
			"Yue"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Yue"
	},
	{
		id: 17,
		question: "Which two air temples exclusively housed female airbenders?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Northern and Southern",
			"Southern and Eastern",
			"Western and Eastern",
			"Northern and Western"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Western and Eastern"
	},
	{
		id: 18,
		question: "What once-in-a-century event increases firebenders' power?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Sozin's comet",
			"Sozin's sun",
			"Sozn's meteor",
			"Sozin's volcano"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Sozin's comet"
	},
	{
		id: 19,
		question: "Toph fights in underground earthbending tournaments under the name...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"The Blind Boulder",
			"The Blind Bandit",
			"The Hippo",
			"Twinkle Toes"
		],
		correctAnswer: "The Blind Bandit"
	},
	{
		id: 20,
		question: "What is the strongest ability that the Avatar can invoke?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"The Avatar Phase",
			"The Avatar's Zenith",
			"Summoning dark spirits",
			"The Avatar State"
		],
		correctAnswer: "The Avatar State"
	},
	{
		id: 21,
		question: "What is the capital of the Earth kingdom?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Ba Sing Se",
			"Kaya's town",
			"Kyoshi Island",
			"Yu Dao"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Ba Sing Se"
	},
	{
		id: 22,
		question: "Zuko's love interest (and one of his sister's best friends) is named...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Ty Lee",
			"Suki",
			"Mai",
			"Ursa"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Mai"
	},
	{
		id: 23,
		question: "The bounty hunter who rides on a shirshu is named...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Mai",
			"June",
			"Ty Lee",
			"Nyla"
		],
		correctAnswer: "June"
	},
	{
		id: 24,
		question: "Who leads the Freedom Fighters?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Haru",
			"Jet",
			"Suki",
			"Iroh"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Jet"
	},
	{
		id: 25,
		question: "Who are the only known firebenders capable of generating lightning?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Ozai, Azula, Iroh",
			"Azula, Iroh, Zuko",
			"Ozai, Azula, Zuko",
			"Sozin, Ozai, Iroh"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Ozai, Azula, Iroh"
	},
	{
		id: 26,
		question: "What phrase makes Appa fly?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Whoa",
			"Yip-yip",
			"Hiyah",
			"Up"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Yip-yip"
	},
	{
		id: 27,
		question: "What is the name of the secret society Iroh belongs to?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"The Order of the Red Lotus",
			"The Order of the White Jasmine",
			"The Order of the White Lotus",
			"The Order of the White Rose"
		],
		correctAnswer: "The Order of the White Lotus"
	},
	{
		id: 28,
		question: "Who teaches Aang firebending?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Iroh",
			"Zuko",
			"Jeong Jeong",
			"Roku"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Zuko"
	},
	{
		id: 29,
		question: "What dark skill can extremely advanced waterbenders do?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Shoot lightning",
			"Summoning evil spirits",
			"Bloodbending",
			"Reading minds"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Bloodbending"
	},
	{
		id: 30,
		question: "Toph creates the earthbending technique...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Bloodbending",
			"Energybending",
			"Lightningbending",
			"Metalbending"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Metalbending"
	},
	{
		id: 31,
		question: "What does the Fire Lord rename himself once he takes over the world?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Dark Lord",
			"High Councilor",
			"Phoenix King",
			"Supreme Leader"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Phoenix King"
	},
	{
		id: 32,
		question: "The Earth kingdom's secret police is called the...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Rough Rhinos",
			"Yuyan Archers",
			"Red Lotus",
			"Dai Li"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Dai Li"
	},
	{
		id: 33,
		question: "Zuko and Azula's mother is named...?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"Ty Lee",
			"Ursula",
			"Ursa",
			"Suki"
		],
		correctAnswer: "Ursa"
	},
	{
		id: 34,
		question: "How does Aang defeat the Fire Lord?",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"He banishes him to the spirit world",
			"He removes his firebending ability",
			"He puts him in a comatose state",
			"He kills him"
		],
		correctAnswer: "He removes his firebending ability"
	},
	{
		id: 35,
		question: "Sokka and Katara are from the Water Tribe of the ____ Pole",
		possibleAnswers: [
			"North",
			"South"
		],
		correctAnswer: "South"
	}
]